export const questions = [
    {
      question: 'Who is a co-founder of Scroll?',
      answers: ['Seung Yoon Lee', 'Sandy Peng', 'Jason Zhao', 'Cecilia Hsueh'],
      correctAnswer: 'Sandy Peng'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which is not EVM compatible?',
      answers: ['Aptos', 'BNB Chain', 'Scroll', 'Metis'],
      correctAnswer: 'Aptos'
    },
    {
      question: 'When was Scroll founded?',
      answers: ['2019', '2020', '2021', '2022'],
      correctAnswer: '2021'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who is a co-founder of Alchemy?',
      answers: ['Stani Kulechov', 'Anatoly Yakovenko', 'Raj Gokal', 'Nikil Viswanathan'],
      correctAnswer: 'Nikil Viswanathan'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the native token of Ethereum?',
      answers: ['ETH', 'BTC', 'SOL', 'BNB'],
      correctAnswer: 'ETH'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which consensus algorithm does Ethereum use after "The Merge"?',
      answers: ['Proof of Work', 'Proof of Stake', 'Proof of History', 'Proof of Authority'],
      correctAnswer: 'Proof of Stake'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is a zk-Rollup?',
      answers: ['New consensus algorithm', 'L2 scaling solution', 'NFT platform', 'Cross-chain bridge'],
      correctAnswer: 'L2 scaling solution'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of the following is a zk-Rollup project?',
      answers: ['StarkNet', 'Solana', 'Avalanche', 'Arbitrum'],
      correctAnswer: 'StarkNet'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of the following is a decentralized oracle provider?',
      answers: ['Uniswap', 'Aave', 'Chainlink', 'Polygon'],
      correctAnswer: 'Chainlink'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is Ethereumâ€™s programming language?',
      answers: ['Rust', 'Solidity', 'JavaScript', 'Go'],
      correctAnswer: 'Solidity'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which is a blockchain explorer for Ethereum?',
      answers: ['Etherscan', 'CoinMarketCap', 'Binance', 'CoinGecko'],
      correctAnswer: 'Etherscan'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which layer is Scroll categorized under?',
      answers: ['Layer 1', 'Layer 2', 'Layer 3', 'Layer 0'],
      correctAnswer: 'Layer 2'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which Ethereum upgrade introduced staking?',
      answers: ['The Merge', 'London Hard Fork', 'Constantinople', 'Beacon Chain'],
      correctAnswer: 'Beacon Chain'
    },
    {
      question: 'What does zk in zk-Rollup stand for?',
      answers: ['Zero Knowledge', 'Zonal Kernel', 'Zero Keys', 'Zone Keeper'],
      correctAnswer: 'Zero Knowledge'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the block time on Ethereum after the merge?',
      answers: ['15 seconds', '10 minutes', '5 minutes', '1 second'],
      correctAnswer: '15 seconds'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is Uniswap?',
      answers: ['CEX', 'A Layer 2 solution', 'DEX', 'Ethereum wallet'],
      correctAnswer: 'DEX'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is MEV?',
      answers: ['Maximum Extractable Value', 'Minimum Exchange Volume', 'Medium Economic Volume', 'Maximized Ethereum Volatility'],
      correctAnswer: 'Maximum Extractable Value'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the token standard for NFTs on Ethereum?',
      answers: ['ERC-20', 'ERC-1155', 'ERC-721', 'ERC-998'],
      correctAnswer: 'ERC-721'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who founded Ethereum?',
      answers: ['Vitalik Buterin', 'Satoshi Nakamoto', 'Stani Kulechov', 'Hayden Adams'],
      correctAnswer: 'Vitalik Buterin'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which Ethereum Improvement Proposal (EIP) introduced fee burning?',
      answers: ['EIP-1559', 'EIP-721', 'EIP-20', 'EIP-2981'],
      correctAnswer: 'EIP-1559'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is ENS?',
      answers: ['Ethereum Name Service', 'Ether Network Switch', 'Ethereum Notification System', 'Enterprise Node Service'],
      correctAnswer: 'Ethereum Name Service'
    },
    {
      question: 'What does Solidity compile down to?',
      answers: ['Bytecode', 'Python', 'Rust', 'WebAssembly'],
      correctAnswer: 'Bytecode'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which blockchain uses a different virtual machine than Ethereum?',
      answers: ['Solana', 'Arbitrum', 'Optimism', 'Scroll'],
      correctAnswer: 'Solana'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which token standard is used for fungible tokens on Ethereum?',
      answers: ['ERC-20', 'ERC-721', 'ERC-1155', 'ERC-998'],
      correctAnswer: 'ERC-20'
    }
]